

Web Developer|front-end developer|UI/UX designer and developer: i am a Wordpress, angular, react developer i currently have 2+ years of work experience. I am looking for a fast pased work environment so i can learn more as a developer. I am a team player but also good at individual work. My interest include playing chess, manga reading and mountain hiking just to name a few. Well lets set up an interview and we will discuss more then

Lethabo Joy Lekoloane

Phone:

+27 722 430 359/+27 670 413 362

E-Mail:

lethabolekoloane11@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/Lethabo-joy-lekoloane-3003881aa

GitHub:

Github.com/lethabolekoloane

Availability:

Limpopo & Gauteng (immediately)

Skill Highlights

- Team Player
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Innovative & Goal driven

Languages

English(good) Sepedi(home language) Zulu / Tshivenda (good)

Education

02/2015-11/2019

BSc Mathematical science(Computer Science & Mathematic) -University of Limpopo ,RSA 01/2010-11/2014 Kgakala sec school bachelor pass

Experience

15/03/2022

Freelance Wordpress developer @ Big On Digital

 Themes, tamplates, design, implimentation and security updates, responsive designs, wireframe designing

Freelance mobile developer @ Agritourza

 Used Angular and Ionic to build mobile apps with the backend consisting of firebase and 3rd party API'S 29/06/2021-30/08/2021

UI/Ux developer @Daita pty(ltd)

- Edited existing figma prototype in a running project
- Worked on the frontend of 2 projects namely (municipal hr. pulse and SiTa hackathon) on a .net and Ashure powered framework

01/04/2021-28/05/2021

Freelance ui/ux figma developer @ Agritourza

• Used Angular to build 20 landing pages with my team and 20 figma prototypes

04/2020-03/2021

Web Developer/fullstack /mobiledeveloper @mLabs codetribe

- Remote learner ship
- Full stack development using, AngularJS, Ionic, firebase and figma ui/ux design

Software skills

FRONTEND

- HTML|CSS|SCSS(skilled)
- JAVASCRIPT|OOP(skilled)
- WORDPRESS
- REACT | REACT NATIVE
- ANGULARJS (skilled)
- IONIC(skilled)
- TYPESCRIPT(skilled)
- C++|JAVA|C#(medium)
- PYTHON(beginner)

BACKEND/DATABASES

- FIREBASE|NODEJS
- SQL
- MONGO DB
 OTHER TOOLS
- API'S
- BOOSTRAP|CORDOVA
- ANGULAR METERIAL UI/UX
- FIGMA|Adobe xd

References

References available on request